长沙市二零二二年初中学业水平考试。
听下面五段对话，每段对话后有一个小题，从题中所给的
三个选项中。
中选出最佳选项。
听完每段对话后，你都有十秒钟的时间来回答有关小题和阅读下一小题。
每段对话读两遍。
I want to be an artist.
Can I help you?
I'd a bowl of beef noodles, please.
听第六段材料，回答第六、七题。
Hello, Mary. How was your trip to Beijing last month?
Wonderful. What did you do there?
I visited the Bird's Nest, the Summer Palace, and the Forbidden City, but the Great
Wall was my favorite part.
Hello, Mary. How was your trip to Beijing last month?
Wonderful. What did you do there?
I visited the Bird's Nest, the Summer Palace,
and the Forbidden City,
听第七段材料，回答第八、九题。
How is it going, Anna?
Terrible. I am having some problems with my math.
It's too difficult for me.
Why not ask your math teacher for help?
She is too busy.
There are always students around her.
Don't worry. I will try my best to help you.
How is it going, Anna?
Terrible. I am having some problems with my math.
It's too difficult for me.
Why not ask your math teacher for help?
She The doctor just told me to be careful about the things I eat.
听第八段材料，回答第十、十一题。
Like what? Well, he told me to eat more vegetables, no more cakes or seafood.
Oh, vegetables. I often have tomatoes.
And the doctor also told me not to any coffee.
That's difficult. I love my coffee in the morning.
I know what you mean.
But drinking too much coffee is not good for your health.
The doctor just told me to be careful about the things I eat.
Like what? Well, he told me to eat more vegetables, no more cakes or seafood.
Oh, vegetables. I often have tomatoes.
And the doctor also told me not to drink any coffee.
That's difficult. I love my coffee in the morning.
I know what you mean.
But drinking too much coffee is not good for your health.
听第九段材料，回答第十二至十四题
Honey, have you done your homework?
Not yet. Then why are you playing the game again?
This is my favorite game.
Go and do your homework.
You can play it after you finish your homework.
But the game will be over then.
There will be another game.
Mom, please. You know the rules.
Rules, I get bored with them.
Honey, have you done your homework?
Not yet. Then why are you playing the game again?
This is my favorite game.
Go and do your homework.
You can play it after you finish your homework.
But the game will be over then.
There will be another game.
Mom, please. You know the rules.
Rules, rules. I get bored with them.
听第十段材料，回答第十五至十七题。
Hey Mike, have you heard David's new song?
No, I lost my earphones just now.
I think I left them on the bus.
Are you sure you didn't leave them in the library?
I don't think so.
I am sure I had them in my pocket when I left there.
You can borrow mine and keep them until tomorrow.
I have another pair in my bag.
Thank you. You are welcome.
Let's listen to the new song.
I'd love to, but now I have to up my sister at the airport.
I will listen to it in the afternoon.
Okay. Don't forget to buy new earphones.
I will. I am going to get one pair in the supermarket tonight.
Hey Mike, have you heard David's new song?
No, I lost my earphones just now.
I think I left them on the bus.
Are you sure you didn't leave them in the library?
I don't think so.
I am sure I had them in my pocket when I left there.
You can borrow mine and keep them until tomorrow.
I have another pair in my bag.
Thank you. You are welcome.
Let's listen to the new song.
I'd love to, but now I have to pick up my sister at the airport.
will listen to it in the afternoon.
Okay. Don't forget to buy new earphones.
I will. I am going to get one pair in
听第十一段材料，回答第十八至二十题。
Peppa Pig is a children's TV show made in the UK,
which is also popular in the USA, Australia and even in China.
It began in 2004 and it has been shown in 180 different countries around the world.
The show is about the life of young pig named Peppa.
She likes to dress up.
She is usually seen in her favorite red dress.
Peppa has many different animal friends.
They enjoy playing together every day.
Peppa likes to do many fun activities, such as biking and swimming.
She lives with her family in a big yellow house on the hill.
She has a little brother called George.
George wears a blue t -shirt and cries a lot.
Dad Pig wears cool glasses and likes to laugh.
And Mom Pig is good at working on her computer.
Peppa Pig is a children's TV show made in the UK,
which is also popular in the USA, Australia and even in China.
It began in 2004 and it has been shown in 180 different countries around the world.
The show is about the life of a young pig named Peppa.
She likes to dress up.
She is usually seen in her favorite red dress.
Peppa has many different animal friends.
They enjoy playing together every day.
Peppa likes to do many fun activities, such as biking and swimming.
She lives with her family in a big yellow house on the hill.
She has a little brother called George.
George wears a blue t -shirt and cries a lot.
Dad Pig wears cool glasses and likes to laugh.
And Mom Pig is good at working on her computer.
二。
听力测试结束，请关注“锦鲤英语”微信公众号